<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Greycat on Matthieu Jimenez Website</title>
    <link>http://jimenez.lu/tags/greycat/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Greycat on Matthieu Jimenez Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://jimenez.lu/tags/greycat/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Greycat AdditionaL Actions</title>
      <link>http://jimenez.lu/project/greycat/gala/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimenez.lu/project/greycat/gala/</guid>
      <description>This library bring additional actions to the Greycat project. This library is compatible with the latest Greycat api (10). Compatibility with previous versions of Greycat (formerly MWDB) api can be found in previous release. The release of the plugin will follow the release of Greycat.
Actions? Actions are reusable elements hiding low-level, asynchronous task primitives behind an expressive API. Actions allows to traverse and manipulate the graph and can be chained to form a task.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greycat Additional Types</title>
      <link>http://jimenez.lu/project/greycat/gat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimenez.lu/project/greycat/gat/</guid>
      <description>Greycat Additional Types The Greycat Additional Types (gat) project is a plugin for Greycat offering additional types to the one natively handled by Greycat. The project currently offers 3 familly of additional types, sets bitset and radix trees. More could be added in the future.
Why additional types? Since V10, Greycat introduce the notion of Custom types that allow a user to store customize attribute in her nodes. This made extension of greycat easier to users, however as the development of custom types might be a bit tedious to new users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paw 4 greycat</title>
      <link>http://jimenez.lu/project/greycat/paw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimenez.lu/project/greycat/paw/</guid>
      <description>This library bring additional functionality to the GreyCat project. This library is compatible with the latest Greycat api.
Token? This project aims at providing a way to tokenize all of string that one might want to store in the graph. In addition to saving space, it also enable further analytics. Every tokenized content being accessible through a vocabulary node globally indexed. The library supports time and world, every new word being created at the Beginning of Time and first world.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>