<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Matthieu Jimenez Website</title>
    <link>http://www.jimenez.lu/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Matthieu Jimenez Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.jimenez.lu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>FSE 2019</title>
      <link>http://www.jimenez.lu/post/fse19/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jimenez.lu/post/fse19/</guid>
      <description>2 weeks ago, I had the chance to assist to FSE&amp;rsquo;19 in Talling to present the final paper of my thesis titled: &amp;ldquo;The Importance of Accounting for Real-World Labelling When Predicting Software Vulnerabilities&amp;rdquo;, which was awarded with a  Distinguished Paper Award .
The paper presents the risks faced when using temporal data to train and evaluate Vulnerability Prediction Models(VPM).
The paper can be found here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thesis Defended</title>
      <link>http://www.jimenez.lu/post/thesisdefended/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jimenez.lu/post/thesisdefended/</guid>
      <description>On October 2nd , I defended my PhD and obtained the grade excellent. My thesis titled Evaluating Vulnerability Prediction Models is available online at the following address thesis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paper Accepted at ICSME and Project added</title>
      <link>http://www.jimenez.lu/post/newpaperandprojectadded/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jimenez.lu/post/newpaperandprojectadded/</guid>
      <description>Following the acceptance of my paper &amp;ldquo;On the Impact of Tokenizer and Parameters on N-Gram Based Code Analysis&amp;rdquo; at ICSME this year, the publication as well as the project section have been updated. Among the two added projects, tuna is the artefact going along with the paper. It contains different utilities such as tokenizer, nGram Model library, defect dataset generator tool as well as the code to reproduce the experiments. While the second added project called data7 corresponds to the refactored version of the vulnerability dataset generator tool used in my previous paper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data7</title>
      <link>http://www.jimenez.lu/project/research/data7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jimenez.lu/project/research/data7/</guid>
      <description>The website for this project can be found here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tuna</title>
      <link>http://www.jimenez.lu/project/research/tuna/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jimenez.lu/project/research/tuna/</guid>
      <description>The website for this project can be found here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>October Update</title>
      <link>http://www.jimenez.lu/post/octoberupdate/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jimenez.lu/post/octoberupdate/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone,
The website have been updated with my latest publications, and as all greycat related project are now hosted by the greycat-incubator on github, the links have been updated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greycat AdditionaL Actions</title>
      <link>http://www.jimenez.lu/project/greycat/gala/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jimenez.lu/project/greycat/gala/</guid>
      <description>This library bring additional actions to the Greycat project. This library is compatible with the latest Greycat api (10). Compatibility with previous versions of Greycat (formerly MWDB) api can be found in previous release. The release of the plugin will follow the release of Greycat.
Actions? Actions are reusable elements hiding low-level, asynchronous task primitives behind an expressive API. Actions allows to traverse and manipulate the graph and can be chained to form a task.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greycat Additional Types</title>
      <link>http://www.jimenez.lu/project/greycat/gat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jimenez.lu/project/greycat/gat/</guid>
      <description>Greycat Additional Types The Greycat Additional Types (gat) project is a plugin for Greycat offering additional types to the one natively handled by Greycat. The project currently offers 3 familly of additional types, sets bitset and radix trees. More could be added in the future.
Why additional types? Since V10, Greycat introduce the notion of Custom types that allow a user to store customize attribute in her nodes. This made extension of greycat easier to users, however as the development of custom types might be a bit tedious to new users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Website</title>
      <link>http://www.jimenez.lu/post/newwebsite/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jimenez.lu/post/newwebsite/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone,
The website has been completely refactored and should hopefully be updated more frequently.
A project section appeared describing the projects I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on or worked on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Structure and Algorithmic</title>
      <link>http://www.jimenez.lu/teaching/algorithmic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jimenez.lu/teaching/algorithmic/</guid>
      <description> Course Description Taught in French.
I&amp;rsquo;m responsible of the practical session of this class and the lectures are given by Pierre Kelsen
Evaluation: Practical sessions (40%), Final Exam (60%)
Description:  Algorithms Complexity Sorting Data Structure Hash Graph  Statistics  ~15 hours of practical session per semester 15 to 50 students  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Files Metrics</title>
      <link>http://www.jimenez.lu/project/utils/filemetrics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jimenez.lu/project/utils/filemetrics/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Written in Kotlin, this project aims at providing a library for computing common metrics of a C file from Java program. The analysis is based on the result provided by the joern tool. To allow a better handling of dependency the tool has been ported organized for maven and only the parts relevant to this project were kept. This version can be found in the joern repository
Use The library is written in Kotlin but can be used from Java.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Computer</title>
      <link>http://www.jimenez.lu/teaching/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jimenez.lu/teaching/intro/</guid>
      <description> Course Description Taught in French.
I&amp;rsquo;m teaching the full class with Pr Le Traon
Evaluation: Final Exam (100%)
Description:  History of Computer Science Binary system Automata Programming history Version Control System Network  Statistics  ~20 hours of class 50 students  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paw 4 greycat</title>
      <link>http://www.jimenez.lu/project/greycat/paw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jimenez.lu/project/greycat/paw/</guid>
      <description>This library bring additional functionality to the GreyCat project. This library is compatible with the latest Greycat api.
Token? This project aims at providing a way to tokenize all of string that one might want to store in the graph. In addition to saving space, it also enable further analytics. Every tokenized content being accessible through a vocabulary node globally indexed. The library supports time and world, every new word being created at the Beginning of Time and first world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software Testing</title>
      <link>http://www.jimenez.lu/teaching/st/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jimenez.lu/teaching/st/</guid>
      <description> Course Description Taught in English.
I&amp;rsquo;m responsible of the practical session of this class and the lectures are given by Pr. Le Traon.
Evaluation: Practical sessions (40%), Final Exam (60%)
Description:  Build Automation Junit 5 Coverage TDD Mutation Testing  Statistics  ~15 hours of practical session per semester 15 students  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tools Utils</title>
      <link>http://www.jimenez.lu/project/utils/toolsutils/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jimenez.lu/project/utils/toolsutils/</guid>
      <description>This library gather all utilitary methods that are used by the different modules of the bugs and vulnerabilities project and that could be used in other context.
Content  Git utilitary + diff MultiThreading Regexp Serialization  Documentation
Git This module provide some useful function when trying to mine a git repository
Use  val git = GitUtilitary(&amp;quot;pathto .git folder&amp;quot;) git.retrievingFileFromSpecificCommit(&amp;quot;hashOfCommit&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;fullpathOfFile&amp;quot;)  Class data class DeveloperHistory(val totalNumberOfDeveloper: Int = 0, val currentNumberOfDeveloper: Int = 0, val numberOfChanges: Int = 0) : Serializable  Methods  retrievingFileFromSpecificCommit listOfCommitImpactingAFile previousCommitImpactingAFile gitBlame gitBlameNbDev getDevHistoryOfAFile (use Developer History class) getDeltaFile (Delta History) getListOfModifiedFile getCommitMessage getTimeCommit  Diff This side module provides methods for computing unified diff or delta of between 2 versions of a file</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>http://www.jimenez.lu/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jimenez.lu/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone,
On this page you will find all relevant information about me. For more detailed information, I invite you to visit my Linkedin
I&amp;rsquo;m currently a research and development engineer at DataThings in Luxembourg. I received an Engineering degree in Computer Science with a major in Information Security from Polytech’Nice Sophia in 2014. I got my PhD in October 2018 at the University of Luxembourg defending a thesis on the Evaluation of Vulnerability Prediction Models.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>http://www.jimenez.lu/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jimenez.lu/publications/</guid>
      <description>PhD Thesis  (2018) Matthieu Jimenez. &amp;ldquo;Evaluating Vulnerability Prediction Models&amp;rdquo; 2 October 2018
 OrbiLu   International Conferences Awarded  (2019) Matthieu Jimenez, Renaud Rwemalika, Mike Papadakis, Federica Sarro, Yves Le Traon, Mark Harman. &amp;ldquo;The Importance of Accounting for Real-World Labelling When Predicting Software Vulnerabilities&amp;rdquo; in Proceedings of the 27th ACM Joint European Software Engineering Conference and Symposium on the Foundations of Software Engineering (ESEC/FSE&amp;rsquo;19), Tallin, Estonia, August 2019</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>research</title>
      <link>http://www.jimenez.lu/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jimenez.lu/research/</guid>
      <description> Here you can access data related to my research
Profiling Android vulnerabilities  Repository  An Empirical Analysis of Vulnerabilities in OpenSSL and the Linux Kernel  Additional Figures  Analyzing Complex Data in Motion at Scale with Temporal Graphs  Benchmark  Enabling the Continous Analysis of Security Vulnerabilities with VulData7  Data7 BugData7  On the Impact of Tokenizer and Parameters on N-Gram Based Code Analysis  Tuna  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>